('Udo', 'PERSON')('Udo', 'PERSON')('Kruschwitz', 'PERSON')('Computation', 'ORGANIZATION')('Group', 'ORGANIZATION')('Essex', 'ORGANIZATION')('LAC', 'ORGANIZATION')('Reading', 'ORGANIZATION')('Group', 'ORGANIZATION')('YPA', 'ORGANIZATION')('BT', 'ORGANIZATION')('Computation', 'ORGANIZATION')('Group', 'ORGANIZATION')('Minority', 'ORGANIZATION')('Rights', 'ORGANIZATION')('Group', 'ORGANIZATION')('IGGI', 'ORGANIZATION')('University', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('York', 'ORGANIZATION')('University', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('Essex', 'ORGANIZATION')('Queen', 'ORGANIZATION')('Mary', 'ORGANIZATION')('University', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('London', 'ORGANIZATION')('Goldsmiths', 'ORGANIZATION')('College', 'ORGANIZATION')('University', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('London', 'ORGANIZATION')('Minority', 'ORGANIZATION')('Rights', 'ORGANIZATION')('Group', 'ORGANIZATION')('Essex', 'ORGANIZATION')('Iraq', 'LOCATION')('Ceasefire', 'LOCATION')('Portal', 'LOCATION')('Signal', 'ORGANIZATION')('Media', 'ORGANIZATION')('Miguel', 'PERSON')('Martinez-Alvarez', 'PERSON')('KTP', 'ORGANIZATION')('Head', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('Research', 'ORGANIZATION')('at', 'ORGANIZATION')('Signal', 'ORGANIZATION')('Miguel', 'PERSON')('KTP', 'ORGANIZATION')('School', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('Computer', 'ORGANIZATION')('Science', 'ORGANIZATION')('and', 'ORGANIZATION')('Electronic', 'ORGANIZATION')('Engineering', 'ORGANIZATION')('Robert', 'PERSON')('Gordon', 'PERSON')('University', 'PERSON')('Aberdeen', 'PERSON')('Open', 'ORGANIZATION')('University', 'ORGANIZATION')('KTP', 'ORGANIZATION')('School', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('Computer', 'ORGANIZATION')('Science', 'ORGANIZATION')('and', 'ORGANIZATION')('Electronic', 'ORGANIZATION')('Engineering', 'ORGANIZATION')('KTP', 'ORGANIZATION')('School', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('Computer', 'ORGANIZATION')('Science', 'ORGANIZATION')('and', 'ORGANIZATION')('Electronic', 'ORGANIZATION')('Engineering', 'ORGANIZATION')('Ipswich', 'ORGANIZATION')('Involvements', 'ORGANIZATION')('Panel', 'ORGANIZATION')('Karen', 'PERSON')('Spärck', 'PERSON')('Jones', 'PERSON')('IRSG', 'ORGANIZATION')('IRSG', 'ORGANIZATION')('Text', 'ORGANIZATION')('Analytics', 'ORGANIZATION')('Meetup', 'ORGANIZATION')('London', 'LOCATION')('London', 'LOCATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Doctoral', 'ORGANIZATION')('Consortium', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('LREC', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Worksop', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')(')', 'ORGANIZATION')('Workshop', 'ORGANIZATION')('on', 'ORGANIZATION')('Recent', 'ORGANIZATION')('Advances', 'ORGANIZATION')('in', 'ORGANIZATION')('News', 'ORGANIZATION')('Information', 'ORGANIZATION')('Retrieval', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('ACHS', 'ORGANIZATION')('Workshop', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')(')', 'ORGANIZATION')('Gamification', 'ORGANIZATION')('for', 'ORGANIZATION')('Information', 'ORGANIZATION')('Retrieval', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')(')', 'ORGANIZATION')('Gamification', 'ORGANIZATION')('for', 'ORGANIZATION')('Information', 'ORGANIZATION')('Retrieval', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Scientific', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Personalised', 'ORGANIZATION')('Multilingual', 'ORGANIZATION')('Information', 'ORGANIZATION')('Access', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Demo', 'ORGANIZATION')('Co-Chair', 'ORGANIZATION')('', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('NAACL', 'ORGANIZATION')('Student', 'ORGANIZATION')('Research', 'ORGANIZATION')('Workshop', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Joint', 'ORGANIZATION')('Workshop', 'ORGANIZATION')('on', 'ORGANIZATION')('Information', 'ORGANIZATION')('Retrieval', 'ORGANIZATION')('and', 'ORGANIZATION')('Hybrid', 'ORGANIZATION')('Machine', 'ORGANIZATION')('Translation', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Hypertext', 'ORGANIZATION')('Workshop', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Student', 'ORGANIZATION')('Research', 'ORGANIZATION')('Workshop', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Essex', 'ORGANIZATION')('Language', 'ORGANIZATION')('and', 'ORGANIZATION')('Computation', 'ORGANIZATION')('Group', 'ORGANIZATION')('(', 'ORGANIZATION')('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')('Committee', 'ORGANIZATION')('Deirdre', 'PERSON')('Lungley', 'PERSON')('Mahmoud', 'PERSON')('El-Haj', 'PERSON')('Sharhida', 'PERSON')('Saad', 'PERSON')('Dr', 'PERSON')('Azhar', 'PERSON')('Alhindi', 'PERSON')('Dr', 'PERSON')('Jon', 'PERSON')('Chamberlain', 'PERSON')('Roseline', 'PERSON')('Antai', 'PERSON')('Fawaz', 'PERSON')('Alarfaj', 'PERSON')('Silviu', 'PERSON')('Paun', 'PERSON')('David', 'PERSON')('Gundry', 'PERSON')('Chris', 'PERSON')('Madge', 'PERSON')('Dino', 'PERSON')('Ratcliffe', 'PERSON')('Steve', 'PERSON')('Zimmerman', 'PERSON')('Publications', 'ORGANIZATION')('Selected', 'ORGANIZATION')('Publications', 'ORGANIZATION')('Foundation', 'ORGANIZATION')('Martin', 'PERSON')('White', 'PERSON')('ACM', 'ORGANIZATION')('Computing', 'ORGANIZATION')('Reviews', 'ORGANIZATION')('Udo', 'ORGANIZATION')('Kruschwitz', 'ORGANIZATION')('University', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('Essex', 'ORGANIZATION')('School', 'ORGANIZATION')('of', 'ORGANIZATION')('Computer', 'ORGANIZATION')('Science', 'ORGANIZATION')('and', 'ORGANIZATION')('Electronic', 'ORGANIZATION')('Engineering', 'ORGANIZATION')('Wivenhoe', 'ORGANIZATION')('Park', 'ORGANIZATION')('Colchester', 'ORGANIZATION')